cashfly.com 2015-12-16

# CashFly : Your Privacy Rights

## Your Privacy Rights

The owner of this website ("CashFly," "we," or "us") makes the CashFly platform which enables the creation of condensed and shortened links to pages that display advertising media, subject to this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") and the CashFly Terms and Conditions. CashFly rewards publishers of the shortened links by offering a percentage of advertising revenues.

This Privacy Policy explains what information we may collect about you and how we may use and maintain the information. By using the CashFly website and/or service, you expressly assent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected from other sources and/or third parties. 

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, IN THEIR ENTIRETY, YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO USE THE WEBSITE OR SERVICE.**

We reserve the right to materially modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you where we deem reasonable and appropriate.

### 1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

CashFly receives information about you from various sources, including, without limitation when you use the CashFly website ("Website"), sign-up to be a user of the CashFly service (the "Service"), when you create an account, and/or from third party websites and services. By using the Website or Service, you are expressly consenting to the collection, transfer, storage, display, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We take your privacy and the security of your personally identifiable information ("PII") and non-personally identifiable information ("NPII") quite seriously. We may collect and store PII, including your name, email address, residential address, telephone number, and data pertaining to both the original and shortened URLs associated with your account. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you and by creating an account on CashFly you allow others to potentially identify you. We may also automatically collect and store NPII including, without limitation, information about your Internet service provider, operating system, type of browser, geographic location, and pages visited. Although NPII is related to you, it is not associated with your PII and cannot be linked to you personally. CashFly may also collect metric and analytic data pertaining to shortened URLs, including, without limitation, IP addresses and physical locations of the devices accessing shortened URLs, referring websites or services, and information regarding the sharing of shortened URLs.

CashFly may use your contact information to send you important information about the Service. Although you may unsubscribe from these messages through your account settings, CashFly reserves the right to contact you when we believe it is necessary.

If you do not want us to collect your PII or NPII and used as provided in this Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Website or Service again.

### 2\. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

The Website and Service are neither intended for, nor directed to, nor to be accessed by, persons under the age of eighteen (18). We do not knowingly collect any information whatsoever from anyone under eighteen (18) years of age.

### 3\. USE AND SHARING OF NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

CashFly automatically gathers certain NPII based on your computer information and stores it in log files. This type of technical and statistical information is used to customize your experience, to help us improve the quality of the Service, and to make your use thereof easy and convenient. We may also collect your IP (Internet protocol) address to help diagnose problems and for administration purposes. We may use cookies, web beacons, clear GIFs, and other monitoring technologies to gather anonymous information. The most common of these technologies are described in more detail below.

**Cookies.** Cookies are small data files that we may place on an individual’s computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with us, and to assist in to track when you have clicked on a CashFly shortened link. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set. We may also use "web beacons" that allow us to access the cookies we set. While some Web browsers allow a user to automatically reject all cookies or be notified when a cookie is about to be placed on the user’s computer, disabling this feature may compromise the efficiency and added services that our cookies provide.

The use of cookies by third party advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Privacy Policy, but is subject to those third parties’ respective privacy policies. If you have an inquiry regarding such third parties’ privacy policies, please visit their respective websites for more information and/or contact them directly.

Your browser has the ability to decline cookies. This is done by setting your browser options to decline all cookies. Our advertisers may download cookies to which we have no control. If used, these cookies are downloaded by clicking on an advertisement found on our website.

**Clear GIFs.** We may employ a common technology known as a "Clear GIF" or "1-by-1 Pixel." A Clear GIF, or "graphic interface format" is a small graphic (in fact, truly a 1×1 pixel) that is placed on a website or in an e-mail. The GIFs do not contain any PII but they, provide us with important information about your use.

**Flash LSOs.** Occasionally, we may use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies.

We may also disclose any of the NPII we may collect in order to comply with applicable laws, respond to governmental inquiries, comply with valid legal process, or protect our rights and property or that of your own.

### 4\. SECURITY

We have implemented technical, administrative and physical security measures to protect information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep information on servers that are protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility accessible only to authorized employees. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though, that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable. Your use of the Website and Service is at your own risk. If you have any questions about security, you can contact us at [security@cashfly.com](mailto:security@cashfly.com).

### 5\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

We may provide links to the websites of many of third party advertisers. If you link to any of these third party websites via the Website or the Service, or to unaffiliated individuals, our terms and privacy policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those websites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these websites, including their terms and privacy policies. We expressly disclaim any and all direct and indirect liability for your interaction with, and the data collection and use practices of, these websites. All inquiries concerning the use of PII by a third party must be communicated to that third party and not to us.

### 6\. ACCOUNT DEACTIVATION

You can delete your account, however, CashFly will first need to verify that you have the authority to so. All activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by CashFly and shall be accessible by the public.

### 7\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third-parties for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third-parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right. You hereby expressly allow us to share information with third- parties for their direct marketing purposes until you remove your information and thus, agreement for such disclosure. To prevent disclosure of your Personal Information for use in direct marketing by a third-party, do not opt-in to such use by providing Personal Information on our Website, or contact us via e-mail to remove your information from our database. Please note that whenever you opt-in to receive future communications from a third- party, your information will be subject to the third-party's privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third-party to use your information, you will need to contact the third-party directly, as we have no control over how third-parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [privacy@cashfly.com](mailto:privacy@cashfly.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address. Please allow 30 days for a response.

### 8\. QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@cashfly.com](mailto:privacy@cashfly.com)

Effective: August 09, 2012
